{"data":[{"question":"If you had any doubts about taking up cycling for health reasons, talk to your doctor and ask his or her advice.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"about","c":"talk","d":"ask","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Had-> have","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The decay begins in a little crack in the enamel to cover of the tooth.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"begins","b":"a little","c":"to cover","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To cover-> covering","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"We should eat food that is good at our teeth and our body.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"should","b":"is","c":"at","d":"teeth","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- At-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Some accidents cause injuries but some lead to die.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"cause","b":"but","c":"some","d":"die","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Die-> death","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The Transport Department organizes road safety campaigns every year in order that reduce traffic accidents.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Transport","b":"safety","c":"in order that","d":"accidents","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- In order that-> in order to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"If everyone takes care when crossing the road, there will be more traffic accidents.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"takes","c":"crossing","d":"more","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- More-> less","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Coffee and tea is favorite hot drinks of people in all parts of the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"and","b":"is","c":"drinks","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"In the United States, which more coffee is used than in any other nation, many people drink their coffee black, without cream or sugar.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"which","c":"any","d":"without","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Which-> where","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"In China, Japan and other Oriental countries, where tea is the national drink, people almost use never sugar in their tea.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Oriental","b":"where","c":"almost","d":"never","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Use never-> never use","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Richard leaves at home at about half past eight, with his schoolbag under his arm.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"at","b":"about","c":"with","d":"under","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Leaves at home-> leaves home","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}